AKKEWACH YODSOMBOON

Software Developer

akkewach.yodsomboon@gmail.com 084-004-5946 https://akkewach.site https://qithub.com/akkewacheiei



Profile

Date of Birth: May 7,1998

Gender: Male **Nationality:** Thai

Language: Thai (Native), English (Basic)

My Introduction

I am a software developer with 4 years of experience in developing both websites and applications, I continue to further my skills to grow in this field.

Work Experience

AUG 2020 - JAN 2024 Wellliness Co.,Ltd.

Junior Developer

- Working collaboratively with a team of UX/UI designers and fitness coaches.
- Developed a platform for online fitness courses that generates workout video schedules tailored to each individual user.
- Continuously adapt and improve the software's features.

JUL 2024 - PRESENT Workmotion Co.,Ltd.

Frontend Developer

- Working collaboratively with a team of UX/UI designers.
- Continuously adapt and improve the software's features.

Education

2016 - 2020 Rajamangala University of Technology Thanyaburi

Bachelor Degrees

Computer Engineering Department, Faculty of Engineering

Skills

Frontend

- Next.js, Nuxt.js
- React.js, Vue.js
- React Native
- Redux
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Ant Design
- TailwindCSS
- Bootstrap

Backend

- Node.js
- Express.js
- Nest.js (Basic)
- REST API
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- ORM (Sequelize)

DevOps / Deployment

- PM2 process manager
- Nginx reverse proxy
- CI/CD pipelines
- Docker (Basic)
- Deployment on Linux server (Ubuntu, DigitalOcean)